sonicdrivein.com 2004-04-11

# SONIC - America's Drive-in

**Information Collection and Use**  
Sonic Corp. ("Sonic") is the sole owner of the information collected on this site and will not sell, share, or lease such information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Sonicdrivein.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration**  
It is unnecessary to register to use this Web site. For users that choose to register, the required contact information, such as name and e-mail address, is clearly noted. This information is used to contact the users about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the users to provide demographic information such as income level and gender.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Our use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes his or her browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, he or she may still use our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Some of our business associates, for example, advertisers, may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over those cookies. Therefore, Sonic and its affiliated entities will not be liable for any damages, injuries, costs, expenses, or privacy issues of any kind directly or indirectly related to our business associates' use of such cookies.

**Log Files**  
We use Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track a user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses may or may not be linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our business associates and some advertisers. This information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may use an outside fulfillment company, but it does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We may use or require the assistance of another party to provide specific services. When a user signs up for these services, we will share names or other contact information that are necessary for the other party to provide these services. These other parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Sonic is not responsible nor liable for the privacy practices or lack of such practices of such other sites. We want our users to be aware of this when they leave our site to visit linked sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Surveys, Contests and Sweepstakes**  
From time to time, our site may request information from users using surveys, contests or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys, contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary. The user has a choice whether to disclose any information by answering the surveys or entering the contests or sweepstakes. Information requested may include contact information (such as user's name and mailing address) and demographic information (such as ZIP code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and services offered by this site.

**Security**  
We take reasonably appropriate precautions on this Web site to protect our users' information. Our users' information collected by us on our Web site, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is maintained and secured in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a marketing professional or a database specialist) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Periodically, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are reminded about the importance we place on privacy and are instructed regarding our policies and procedures for proper use and safeguarding of our users' information. Finally, the servers that we use to store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Special Offers**  
We send all new registering users a welcoming e-mail to verify registration. Registered users may occasionally receive information on products, services or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to registered users to avoid receiving these types of communications. Please see our Choice and Opt-out section below.

**Service Updates**  
We send registered users service announcement updates, such as the launch of new products or promotions. We communicate with the registered users to provide requested services and to respond to various inquiries and issues using e-mail or direct mail. Registered users are able at all times to unsubscribe from all service updates.

**Site Updates**  
We send registered users site announcement updates, such as the addition of new sections to the site or new site features. We communicate with the registered users to provide requested updates and to respond to various inquiries and issues using e-mail or direct mail. Registered users are able at all times to unsubscribe from all site updates.

**Choice and Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to opt out of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. For example, our registration form has an opt-out mechanism so that users who register with us, but do not want any marketing material sent to them, can keep their e-mail address and direct mail addresses off of our lists. Registered users who no longer wish to receive promotional materials or updates from us or our business associates may opt out to avoid receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions contained within each communication. Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so that our users can make an informed choice about whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

**Children**  
Sonic is very sensitive to children's privacy issues and does not associate cookie data with personal information about children. Sonic encourages parents and guardians to supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers. These tools can prevent children from disclosing their name, address, and other personal information online without parental consent. It is Sonic's policy that visitors under 18 years of age should not submit any information on Sonicdrivein.com without parental consent.

**Notification of Changes**  
We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Web site so that our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we will disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by e-mail. Users will have a choice whether we may use their information in this different manner.

If you have any questions about our Web site's privacy policy, you can contact our corporate office.
